{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Basement or Foundation Waterproofing Companies","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40163/":{"taskOID":40163,"originalTaskOID":40163,"setID":473,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":7084,"questionDisplayText":"Problems","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What problems are you having with the foundation? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3902,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Mold, mildew, and/or fungus","answerDisplayText":"Mold, mildew, and/or fungus","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2273,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Excessive dampness","answerDisplayText":"Excessive dampness","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1942,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Discoloration, odors, or rust","answerDisplayText":"Discoloration, odors, or rust","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6953,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"White powder or spots on walls","answerDisplayText":"White powder or spots on walls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2902,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Hairline cracks","answerDisplayText":"Hairline cracks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":960,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Basement flooding","answerDisplayText":"Basement flooding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1153,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Buckling or bowing walls","answerDisplayText":"Buckling or bowing walls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3992,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Mud or clay silt surfacing inside","answerDisplayText":"Mud or clay silt surfacing inside","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1648,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Corners shifting and cracking","answerDisplayText":"Corners shifting and cracking","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4961,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Floor dropping or other changes","answerDisplayText":"Floor dropping or other changes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1140,"questionDisplayText":"Condition of Foundation","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the current condition of the foundation area that needs waterproofing?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10760,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wall is exposed","answerDisplayText":"Wall is exposed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10761,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Wall is not exposed","answerDisplayText":"Wall is not exposed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5620,"questionDisplayText":"Kind of Foundation","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of foundation do you have?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4837,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Poured concrete slab foundation","answerDisplayText":"Poured concrete slab foundation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17425,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Brick or stone foundation","answerDisplayText":"Brick or stone foundation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4832,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Poured concrete basement","answerDisplayText":"Poured concrete basement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3295,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Insulated concrete foundation","answerDisplayText":"Insulated concrete foundation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1558,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Concrete block foundation","answerDisplayText":"Concrete block foundation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1574,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Concrete pier foundation","answerDisplayText":"Concrete pier foundation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4833,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Poured concrete with crawl space","answerDisplayText":"Poured concrete with crawl space","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":13,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":7084,"questionDisplayText":"Problems","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What problems are you having with the foundation? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3902,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Mold, mildew, and/or fungus","answerDisplayText":"Mold, mildew, and/or fungus","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2273,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Excessive dampness","answerDisplayText":"Excessive dampness","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1942,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Discoloration, odors, or rust","answerDisplayText":"Discoloration, odors, or rust","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6953,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"White powder or spots on walls","answerDisplayText":"White powder or spots on walls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2902,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Hairline cracks","answerDisplayText":"Hairline cracks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":960,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Basement flooding","answerDisplayText":"Basement flooding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1153,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Buckling or bowing walls","answerDisplayText":"Buckling or bowing walls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3992,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Mud or clay silt surfacing inside","answerDisplayText":"Mud or clay silt surfacing inside","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1648,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Corners shifting and cracking","answerDisplayText":"Corners shifting and cracking","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4961,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Floor dropping or other changes","answerDisplayText":"Floor dropping or other changes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3902,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Mold, mildew, and/or fungus","answerDisplayText":"Mold, mildew, and/or fungus","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2273,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Excessive dampness","answerDisplayText":"Excessive dampness","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1942,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Discoloration, odors, or rust","answerDisplayText":"Discoloration, odors, or rust","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6953,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"White powder or spots on walls","answerDisplayText":"White powder or spots on walls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2902,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Hairline cracks","answerDisplayText":"Hairline cracks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":960,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Basement flooding","answerDisplayText":"Basement flooding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1153,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Buckling or bowing walls","answerDisplayText":"Buckling or bowing walls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3992,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Mud or clay silt surfacing inside","answerDisplayText":"Mud or clay silt surfacing inside","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1648,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Corners shifting and cracking","answerDisplayText":"Corners shifting and cracking","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4961,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Floor dropping or other changes","answerDisplayText":"Floor dropping or other changes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1140,"questionDisplayText":"Condition of Foundation","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the current condition of the foundation area that needs waterproofing?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10760,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wall is exposed","answerDisplayText":"Wall is exposed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10761,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Wall is not exposed","answerDisplayText":"Wall is not exposed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10760,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wall is exposed","answerDisplayText":"Wall is exposed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10761,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Wall is not exposed","answerDisplayText":"Wall is not exposed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5620,"questionDisplayText":"Kind of Foundation","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of foundation do you have?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4837,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Poured concrete slab foundation","answerDisplayText":"Poured concrete slab foundation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17425,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Brick or stone foundation","answerDisplayText":"Brick or stone foundation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4832,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Poured concrete basement","answerDisplayText":"Poured concrete basement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3295,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Insulated concrete foundation","answerDisplayText":"Insulated concrete foundation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1558,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Concrete block foundation","answerDisplayText":"Concrete block foundation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1574,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Concrete pier foundation","answerDisplayText":"Concrete pier foundation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4833,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Poured concrete with crawl space","answerDisplayText":"Poured concrete with crawl space","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4837,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Poured concrete slab foundation","answerDisplayText":"Poured concrete slab foundation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17425,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Brick or stone foundation","answerDisplayText":"Brick or stone foundation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4832,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Poured concrete basement","answerDisplayText":"Poured concrete basement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3295,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Insulated concrete foundation","answerDisplayText":"Insulated concrete foundation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1558,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Concrete block foundation","answerDisplayText":"Concrete block foundation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1574,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Concrete pier foundation","answerDisplayText":"Concrete pier foundation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4833,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Poured concrete with crawl space","answerDisplayText":"Poured concrete with crawl space","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":13,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/40163/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40163,"taskName":"Foundation or Basement - Waterproofing","taskDescription":"Waterproof a Basement or Foundation","xmTaskDescriptor":"Basement or Foundation Waterproofing Companies","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":21,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Basement  Waterproof Foundation Waterproofing","textMessagingName":"Seal Foundation","rolloverLongDesc":"Usually put in at the same time as the foundation to prevent wet basement problems. Parging is a smeared coat of concrete. Typically this is covered with a coat of tar.","rolloverShortDesc":"Seal outside of foundation.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Waterproof a Basement or Foundation.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Basement Waterproofing Companies \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Waterproof Foundation","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":83,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Waterproofing Foundation or Basement","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Foundation or Basement - Waterproofing","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Foundation or Basement Waterproofing Project","urlName":"Foundation-or-Basement-Waterproofing","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Basement Waterproofing Companies - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","searchKeywords":"Basement,,Waterproof,Foundation,Waterproofing,flood,,resistent","emcCategoryOid":-12033,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":473,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}